<!-- Name: Mingyu Liu -->
<!-- Email: liu.mingyu5@northeastern.edu -->

<topics>
  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-league-of-nations</id>
    <results>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030193/1918-01-08/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva&amp;st=image&amp;r=-0.918,-0.048,2.835,1.284,0</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            SUMMARY OF WILSON'S
            nr.rn m rnr rAMinrnn
            rKUUKAiVl IU WHUKCaS
            FOR WORLD PEACE
            WASHINGTON, Jan. 8. President Wilson in an address to Con
            gress io-day restated American war aims in agreement with the recent
            declaration by the Urilish Premier, David Lloyd George.
            The President presented a definite programnu for world peace con
            taining fourteen specific considerations, as follows:
            "1 Open covenants of peace without private interna
            tional understandings.
            "2 Atijolute freedom of the seas in peace or war, ex
            cept as they may be closed by international action.
            "3 Removal of all economic barriers and establishment
            of equality of trade conditions among nations consenting to
            peace and associating themselves for its maintenance.
            "4 Guarantees for the reduction of national armaments
            to the lowest point consistent with domestic safety.
            "5 Impartial adjustment of all colonial claims based
            upon the principle that the peoples concerned have equal
            weight with the interest of the Government.
            "6 Evacuation of nil Russian territory and opportunity
            for Russia's political development.
            "7 Evacuation of Belgium without any attempt to
            limit her sovereignty.
            "8 All French territory to be freed and restored, and
            reparation for the taking of Alsace-Lorraine.
            "9 Readjustment of Italy's frontiers along clearly
            recognizable lines of nationality.
            "10 Freest opportunity for autonomous development
            of the peoples of Austria-Hungary.
            "11 Evacuation of Roumnnin, Serbia and Montenegro,
            with access to the sea for Serbia, and international guaran
            tees of economic and political independence and territorial
            integrity of the Balkan states.
            "12 Secure sovereignty for Turkey's portion of the
            Ottoman Empire, but with other nationalities under Turkish
            rule assured security of life and opportunity for autonomous
            development, with the Dardanelles permanently opened to
            all nations.
            "13 Establishment of an independent Polish state, in
            cluding territories inhabitated by indisputably Polish popula
            tion, with free access to the sea and political and economic
            independence and territorial integrity guaranteed by inter
            national covenant.
            "14 General association of nations under specific
            covenants for mutual guarantees of political independence
            and territorial integrity to large and small states alike.
            "For such arrangements and
            elusion, "we are willing to fight and continue to fight until they are but ,0 kefip whal they have got Thc negotlations hav5 b4fin f
            achieved, but only because we wish the right to prevail and desire aThe Russian reprcsenta(im w sincere and in carnfit. Th.y cannol
            just and stable peace.' nronou f rnn,... nnfj Hnminniinn
            .Such a programme, he said, removed chief provocations for war.
            "The moral climax (if thi, the culminating and linal war for
            human liberty has come," said the President in ending his address, "and
            thev (people of the United States) arc ready to put their own strength,
            their own highest purpose, their own integrity and devotion to the test.''
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86071134/1919-01-26/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            LEAGUE OF NATIONS IDEA IS ADOPTED
            CONFERENCE

            APPROVES OF PRESIDENT
            WILSON'S PROPOSITIONS
            President Wilaon and Colonel House Arc Named a The
            American, Representatives on Commission to Elaborate
            A Constitution For the League Including lis Preroga
            tives Would Guarantee Peace
            An Integral Part Of The Treaty
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026749/1919-02-14/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
            PARIS, Feb. 14. -The foil text and covenant of the League of
            Nations was officially announced today as follows:
            COVENANT PREAMBLE
            "In order to promote international co-operation and to secure
            international peace and security, by the acceptance of obligations not
            to resort to war, by the prescription of open, just, and honorable re
            lations between nations, by the firm establishment of the understand
            ings of international law as the actual role of conduct among govern
            ments, and by the maintenance of justice and a scrupulous respect
            for all treaty obligations in the dealings of organized peoples with
            one another, the powers signatory to this covenant adopt this con
            stitution of the League of Nations.
            "ARTICLE ONE.
            "The action of the high contracting parties under the terms of
            this covenant shall be effected through the instrumentality of meet
            ing of a body of delegates representing the high contracting parties,
            of meetings at more frequent intervals of an executive council and
            of a permanent international secretariat to be established at the seat
            ot the league.
            "ARTICLE TWO.
            "Meetings of the body of delegates shall be held at stated inter
            vals and from time to time as occasion may require for the purpose of
            dealing with matters within the sphere of action of the league. Meet
            ings of the body of delegates shall be held at the seat of the league or
            at-such other place as may be found convenient and shall consist of
            representatives of high contracting parties. Each jof the. contracting
            parties shall have one vote, but may have not more than ihree rep
            resentatives. L
            "ARTICLE THREE.
            "The executive council shall consist of representatives of the
            United States of America, the British Empire, France, Italy, and
            Japan, together with representatives of four other stales, members
            of the league. The selection of these four states shall In made by the
            body of delegates on such principles and in such manner as they think
            fit. Pending the appointment of these representatives of the other
            states representatives of shall all be members of the executive
            council. Meetings of the council shall be held from time to time as
            occasion may require and at least once a year at whatever place may
            be decided on, or failing any such decision, at the seat of the league,
            and any matter within the sphere of action of the league or affecting
            the peace of this world may be dealt with at such meetings. Invita
            tions shall be sent to any power to attend a meeting of the council at
            which matters directly affecting its interests are to be discussed, and
            no decision taken at any meeting will be binding on such power un
            less so invited.
            "ARTICLE FOUR.
            "All matters of procedure at meetings of the body of delegates
            or the executive council, including the appointment of committees to
            investigate particular matters, shall be regulated by the body of
            delegates or the executive council, and may be decided by a majority
            of the states represented at the meeting. The first meeting of the
            body of delegates and of the executive council shall bo summoned by
            the President of the United States of America.
            "ARTICLE FIVE.
            "The permanent secretariat of the league .shall be established
            :l which shall constitute the seat of the league. The secre
            tariat shall comprise such secretaries and staff as may be required
            under the general direction and control of a secretary general of
            the league, who shall be chosen by the executive council; the secre
            tariat shall be appointed by tho secretary general subject to con
            firmation by the executive council. The secretary general shall act
            in that capacity at all meetings of the body of delegates or of the
            executive council. The expenses of the secretariat shall be borne by
            the states members of the league, in accordance with the apportion
            ment of the expenses of the international bureau of the universal
            postal union.
            "ARTICLE SIX.
            "Representatives of the high contracting parties and officials of
            the league, when engaged on the business of the league, shall enjoy
            diplomatic privileges and immunities, and the buildings occupied by
            the league or its officials or by representatives attending its meetings
            shall enjoy the benefits of extraterritoriality.
            "ARTICLE SEVEN. J w
            "Admission to the league of states not signatories to the covenant
            and not named in the protocol hereto as states to be invited to adhere
            to the covenant requires the assen t of not less than two-thirds of the
            states represented in the body of delegates and shall be limited to
            fully self-governing countries, including dominions and colonies. No
            state shall be admitted to the league unless it is able to give effective
            guarantees of its sincere intention to observe its international obliga
            tions and unless it shall conform to such principles as may be pre
            scribed by the league in regard to its naval and military forces and ar
            maments. "ARTICLE EIGHT.
            "The high contracting parties recognize the principle that the
            maintenance of peace will require the reduction of national arma
            ments to the lowest point consistent with national safety and the
            enforcement by common action of international obligations, having
            special regard to the geographical situation and circumstances of each
            state; and the executive council shall formulate plans for effecting
            such reduction. The executive council shall also determine for the
            consideration and action of the several governments that military
            equipment and armament is fair and reasonable in. proportion to the
            scale, of forces laid down iri the program of disarmament; and these
            iimits, when adopted, shall not be exceeded without iha permission of
            the executive council.
            "The high contracting parties agree that the manufacture by
            private enterprise of munitions and implements of war lends itself
            to grave objections, and direct the executive council to advise how
            the evil effects attendant upon such manufacture can be prevented,
            due regard being had to the necessities of the countries which are
            not able to manufacture for themselves the munitions and implements
            of war necessary for their safety.
            "The high contracting parties undertake in no way to conceal
            from each other the conditions of such of their industries as are capa
            ble of being adapted to warlike purposes or the scale of their anna
            men ts, and agree that there shall be full and frank, interchange of
            information as to their militarv and naval programs.
            "ARTICLE NINE.
            "A permanent commission shall be constituted to advise the league
            on the execution of the provisions of Article Eight and on military and
            naval questions generallv.
            "ARTICLE TEN.
            "The high contracting parties undertake to respect and preserve
            as against external aggression the territorial integrity and existing
            political independence of all states members of the league. In case
            of any such aggression, or in case of any threat or danger of such
            aggression, the executive council shall advise upon the means by
            which the obligation shall be fulfilled.
            "ARTICLE ELEVEN.
            "Any war or threat of war, whether immediately affecting any of
            the high contracting parties or not, is hereby declared a matter of
            concern to the leauo, and the high contracting parties reserve the
            right to take any action that may be deemed wise and effectual to
            safeguard the peace of nations.
            "It is hereby also declared and agreed to be the friendly right of
            ?acli of the high contracting parties to draw the attention of the body
            of delegates or of the executive council to any circumstances affecting
            international intercourse which threaten to disturb international
            peace or the good understanding between nations upon which peace
            lepends.
            "ARTICLE TWELVE.
            "The high contracting parlies agree that should dispute arise
            between them which cannot be adjusted by the ordinal- processes of
            diplomacy they will in no case resort to war without previously
            submitting the questions and matters involved either to arbitration
            or to inquiry by the executive council and until three months after
            J he award by the arbitrators or a recommendation by the executive
            council, and they will not even then resort to war as against a mem-
            Continued on Page 2, Column 1)
            ALLIES SOLID
            WITHSUPPORT
            ESIOENI
            READS DRAFT
            By FRED S. FERGUSON,
            United Press Staff" Correspondent.
            PARIS, Feb. 14. The first world
            constitution was made public this af
            ternoon when President Wilson read
            the draft of the league of nations er
            ganizaticn before the general peac
            congress.
            "While not containing a provisioa
            for any sort of international police
            force, the constitution iwciwie
            striegent-raeasures designed to prc
            ventfuture' wars. I -case any na
            tion makes war without first submit
            ting the questions at issue to arbitra
            tion there are the following possible
            courses open to the league:
            Slay Combine Against Olfcwter.
            Severance of diplomatic relations
            between members of tho league asi
            the recalcitrant power.
            Economic blockade of ihe nation
            refusing arbitration.
            Recommendation by the executive
            council fccforc the use of force.
            The use of force, however, will
            leave to each power freedom of ac
            tion under its action to make the
            necessary declarations of war.
            The international police force, or
            general staff, urged by the French,
            and put to a vote yesterday after
            noon after a stirring speech by Sen
            ator Kourgcois was overwhelmingly
            defeated. Only the French and
            Czechs-Slovaks voted in favor o it.
            With this feature eliminated the con
            stitution was adopted unanimously.
            Add Five New Articles.
            The constitution includes a pre
            amble and twenty-six articles,
            having teen increased from the orig
            inal twenty-two articles during yes
            terday's session of the league com
            mittee. The last articles arc devoted
            to purely parliamentary matters, the
            others covering organization of the
            league.
            Congratulations on securing adop
            tion of the league constitution poured
            in to American headquarters at the
            Hotel Crillon before this afternoon's
            plenary session. Members of the
            League to Enforce Peace declared
            this "is the golden day in the history
            of the world." They declared that,
            despite rumors circulated in Paris
            France s solidly behind the league
            plan.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1919-03-04/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
            37 Senators Reject Wilson's Peace League Plan;
            Demand Swiit Settlement With Germany First
            16,000 to
            Strike at
            6 A. M. in
            N. Y. Harbor
            100,000 To Be Affected
            if Plans of the Union
            Leaders for Tie-Up of
            AH Crafts Succeed
            Yraiy and Navy
            Tugs Will Work
            Police Prepare to Take
            Caro of Crowds That
            Rush to Tunnels;
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1919-04-12/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Lord Robert Ceril Comes
              Out Flatly in Support of
              Wilson. and League Clause
              Is Adopted Without Vote
              PARIS, April 11 (By The Associated
              |Pres3).--Discussion of the Monroe
              Doctrine amendment by the league of
              nations commission last night is de?
              scribed by those present as having
              been nf a dramatic character, conclud
              ing with a speech by President Wilson
              deprecating the opposition which had
              been expressed nnd upholding the doc?
              trine as one of the great bulwarks
              against absolutism. The debate came
              lato in the session, after other sub
              jects had been passed upon.
              The British attitude had been in
              doubt until the last, but Lord Robert.
              Cecil turned the scales by announcing
              that he savv no objection in the amend?
              ment in the form presented by the
              President. M. Larnaude, of the French
              delegation, followed Lord Robert with
              objections to inserting the Monroe
              Doctrine.
              The Chinese also offcred objection to
              the amendment on the ground that its
              i language war. so extended that it might
              validate certain principles and claims
              J affecting Chinese affairs.
              Tho President paid thc closest at-
              tention to the opposition to the amend?
              ment and jotted down notes for a re?
              ply. In his speech the President spoke
              with great enrnestness and with some
              evidence of feeling.
              The President declared the .Monroe
              Doctrine was enunciated t.o combat. the
              Holy Alliance nnd to hold back the
              throat of absolutism which was then
              menacing Europe and seeking to spread
              its power to the Western Hemisphere.
              It. served its purpose in keeping this
              absolute power from the Wesvtern
              World
              One of its great purposes, he said,
              was to raaintain territorial and politi?
              cal integrity, and. having served its
              great purpose in the Western World, it
              now was being brought to the lands
              which had felt the hand of absolutism
              and militarism. It was a source of sur
              prise and discouragement, the Presi?
              dent said, to hear opposition expressed
              to such a doctrine and such a purpose.
              The President's speech closed thc
              4iscussion. There was no vote, and,
              when there were no further remarks,
              the chairman of the meeting said the
              amendment would be considered adopt?
              ed. The commission thi n took up the
              next article of the covenant.
              While the text of the .Monroe amend?
              ment is withheld, its main features are
              substantially along the following line
              "Article X -Nothing in this cove?
              nant shall be construed as invali
              dating any agreement, such as th"
              Monroe Doctrine, for the maintcnanc
              of peace."
              The exact language of the amend?
              ment ia closely guard* d, and i ffoi
              to obtain a copy of the text met with
              the statement that although there iS
              peculiar American interest in the
              announcement there was 110 reason or
              departing from the definite policy 0f
              tiie commission not to disclose textual
              changes in the covenant as the wort
              progresses.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045211/1920-01-16/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              By the Associated Tress
              Paris, .Tan. 10. Representatives' of
              France, Great Britain, Italy, Greece,
              Belgium, Spain, Japan and Brazil,
              members of the council of the
              league of nations, met in the clock room
              of the French foreign office at 10 o'clock
              this morning for the first meeting in the
              history of tho league.
              The council organized at 10:.10 o'clock
              by electing Leon Bourgeois chairman,
              and confirming the choice of Sir Eric
              Drummond, of Great Britain, as general
              secretary.
              The first official act of the council
              was the appointment of a commission to
              trace upon the spot the frontiers of the
              territory of the Sarrc basin.
              j Irish Attach League
              The council received the first formI
              ipiotest to be presented to It almost
              1 before it came into bing. The pro
              test was irom "the envoys 01 the
              elected government of the Irish Repub
              lic" against "the unreal English simu
              lacrum of an international league of
              peace."
              No melition of the nrntrat. wim ma7
              during the meeting of the council, buti -t
              iuinra were nanuea to the newspaper;
              I corrcapondents after thev Ipft tn fwilsMt
              1 eign ofhee. The document was sisnwlis&amp;N
              Ouaklaigh Duffy." It registered "ob-i?
              lections, in -the "pretended league- VitLJUU
              I naiious, and declared the league to be
              an engine of empire, designed to Se
              cure and jierpetuato English hegemony
              throughout both hemispheres."
              I The protest insisted that the league
              was illusory and incomplete, lacking
              authority and sanction, nnd declared
              that the I'nited States stood out "in
              indignation and repudiation" of it.
              Bourgeois Addresses Council
              I.con Bourgeois. French representa
              tive, who presided, said in his openinjt
              address
              "Tho task of presiding at this meet
              ing and inaugurating this great inter
              national institution should have fallen
              ro President Wilson. We respect the
              jeasons which still delay final decision
              by our friends in Washington, but ex
              press the hope that their difficulties will
              soon be overcome and thnt a represen
              tative of the great American republic
              will occupy the place uwaiting him
              among u..
              "The work of tho council will nn
              assume definite character and will have
              that particular force which should be
              associated with our work.
              "January 10, 1020, will go down in
              history as the date of the birth of a
              new world. Decisions- to bo reached
              today will be in Mho name of all na
              tions adhering to the covenant nt i,
              I league. It will be the first decree of all
              free nations leaguing themselves to
              I gether, for the first time in the world,
              to substitute right for might
              1 "But the organization of the league
              of nations will not be complete until
              the assembly of all the states meets."
              British Loyal to League
              Hail Carzon. British secretary ef
              state tor foreign affairs, and that bu
              tion"s representative on the council of
              the league, said
              ';Ou behalf of the British empire I
              1 desire to express the lojaltv of my gov-
              miu-ui. .win mi- exiernni dominions of
              the British crown to the spirit under -l.ving
              the covenant of the league of
              nations. It is our intention by every
              means in our power to insure its prac
              tical efficieucv
              "It is our firm belief
              its instrumentality alone
              to insure that such miseries that tb
              world has experienced during the past
              thnt through
              we can hope
              mssiyasM
              iwsme waiiiig or ine storm to break.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88084272/1920-01-16/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              League Of Nations
              Convenes In Paris
              Without America
              Leon Bourgeois, French Representative, Calls Meeting
              to Order in Absence of President Wilson; Declares
              Day Will Go Down in History as Birth of New
              World; worK or tne uouncu is not uompieie.
              ARIS. France Jan t Bepre-
              i sentatives of France Great Brit
              ain. Italy, Greece, Belgium. Spain.
              Japan and Brazil, members of the
              council of the league of nations, met
              to the -dock room" of the French
              foreign office at 10 oclock this morn
              ing" for the first meeting in the his
              tory of the league
              The council organised at 10 30
              oclock by electing Leon Bourgeois
              chairman and confirming the choice
              of Sir Brie Drummond of Great
              Britain as general secretary
              The first official net of the
              counell wa the appointment of
              a commission to trace upon the
              spot the frontier of the terri
              tory of the Sarre bait la.
              Leon Bourgeois. French represen
              tative, who presided, said "The task
              of presiding at this meeting and in
              augurating this great international
              institution should have fallen to
              president Wilson We recent the
              reasons which still delay final de
              cision by our friends in Washington,
              but express the hope that their diffi
              culties will soon be overcome and
              that a representative of the great
              American republic will occupy the
              place awaiting him among us. The
              work of the council will then assume
              definite character and will have that
              particular force which should be as
              sociated with our work
              Birth of Aew 'Nation."
              "January 16, 120. will go down in
              history as the date of the birth of a
              new world. Decisions to be reached
              today will be in the name of all na
              tions adhering to the covenant of the
              league.
              It will be the flrat decree of
              all free nations leamilnc them
              welve together, for the first time
              la the world to substitute rla-ht
              for might. But the organisation
              of Ihe league of nation will not
              be complete until the assembly
              of nil the states meet.
              1aavi nwtnn nr4lal rtirff t.t
              state for foreign affair and that
              nation's representative on the coon-
              .i r ..j I
              -On behalf of the British empire
              I desire to express the loyalty of my
              government and the external domin-'
              ions of the British 'crown to the spirit
              underlying the covenant of the league
              of nations. It ia our intention by
              every means In our power to insure
              Its oracucal exiteieacr it ts our
              firm belief that through Its instru
              mentality alone we can hope to in
              sure that such miseries that the
              world has experienced during the
              past five year shall not be repeated
              ana mat a new era oi international
              relationship shall dawn.
              "V Universal Desire.
              "The league of nations is an ex
              pression of the universal desire for
              saner methods of regulating affairs
              of mankind, and provides machinery
              by which practical effect may be
              given the principles of international
              friendship and good understanding
              The success of the labors of the peace
              conference ts a good augury for the
              future of the league of nations. For
              the first time an attempt was made
              to bring together under the ausnices
              iot tne league representatives oi gov
              ernments, employes and labors and
              an advance exceeding the results of
              the entire work of th" previous quar
              ter of a tentury has be n made in
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1920-11-14/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Wilson+League+Geneva</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              League Meets
              In Geneva; 41
              Nations There
              All Delegates Present Ex?
              cept Balfour, of England,
              Who Is 111; Swiss
              Try to Assist Covenant
              Germany the Big Issue
              Lloyd George Is Expected
              to Swing the Assembly on
              the Important Question

              By Arthur S. Draper
              Special Cable tn The Tribune
              Copyright, 1920. New York Tribune Inr.
              GENEVA, Nov. 13.?The scenery is
              all set for the opening of the League
              of Nations assembly Monday. All the
              delegates from forty-one countries are
              now present, with the notable exception
              of Arthur Balfour, of Great Britain,
              who has been slightly ill and will not
              reach Geneva until the middle of the
              week.
              Elaborate preparations have b?en
              made for the first historic meeting in
              the Hall of Reformation. The flags of
              twoscore states, with the exception of
              the United States, Germany and Rus?
              sia, are flying from the hotels and pub?
              lic buildings, while the hall itself is a
              mass of color.
              Geneva is just beginning to realize
              what an important responsibility it ac?
              cepted when it became the headquar?
              ters of the League of Nations, but it is
              Handling the unexpectedly large num?
              ber of distinguished visitors in a way
              such as only experienced hosts could.
              The state authorities are making'
              every effort to assist the league. Mo*v i
              of the Swiss are sincere supporters of:
              the organization.
              Germany the Big Issue
              The final meeting of the league coun-
              eil before the assembly gave the mem- j
              bers an opportunity to consider the
              program to be followed at the meetings
              at this place and to canvass opinion
              j on such questions as mandates, the
              protection of minorities, international
              finance and the Polish-Lithuanian dis-
              pute. Although all of these matters
              are to be under discussion, that of j
              chief importance among them all is
              Germany.
              Most of the delegates arrived with
              instructions as to their attitude to?
              ward the .admission of Germany to the
              league, but the situation shifts hourly
              and it is difficult to say exactly what
              the final turnup will be. Lloyd George
              is expected to make a dramatic ap?
              pearance some day next week and
              (Continued on page three)
              Turkish Nationalists
              Proclaim Soviet Rule
              Mustapha Kemal Named Peo?
              ple's Commissariat; Forces
              ('ailed to Smyrna Front
              PARIS, Nov. 13. -A Bavas Agency
              dispatch from Constantinople, dated
              'Thursday, says the Nationalist A.ssem-
              bly at Angora has adopted sovietism i
              i and proclaimed Mustapha Kemal, the
              Turkish .\ationa! Leader, as the people's j
              i commissariat.
              The military council at Angora is
              declared to have decided to transfer
              i the National forces to the Smyrna
              front when the operations in Armenia
              i are concluded.
          </text>
      </result>

      <!-- 5 additional -->
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026853/1919-03-07/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=league+of+nations&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.364,-0.021,1.728,1.728,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Resolved, That America Should Join
              the League of Nations.
              AFFIRMATIVE.
              America should join the League to
              protect tc* liberties of the world.
              t? :J~?4- w;i_
              (If we do tot join, as riesmcuu
              son sayi, '^e will set up a great j
              ideal oi liberty' and then refuse to;
              aid th? Drld to win the privileges!
              which we ourselves enjoy. But, to j
              do this would be against the principles
              which Washington fought for;
              it would be contrary to the ideals
              which sent our sons to France. The
              oppressed peoples of Europe look to
              us to show them the way to freedom.
              We are today the hope of the world.
              Quoting further from Wilson's
              speech at Boston: "If America were
              of +Vmc -innM-nre to fail the world,'
              I what would come of it? Men will be
              thrown back upon the bitterness, not;
              only the disappointment, but also
              the bitterness of despair. Think of;
              the picture?think of the utter blackness
              that would fall upon the world.,
              America has failed I America made,
              a little essay at generosity and then
              withdrew.
              America said, 'We are your
              friends,' but it was only for today,,
              not for tomorrow. America said,;
              'Here is our power to vindicate right' j
              and the next day said, 'Let right take
              care of itself, and we will take care,
              of ourselves.' America said, 'Wej
              set up a light to lead men along the
              lik?*?4-xr Tirn liovo IaW-!
              UB pauis Ul liUCl l/J f I/Wif nv "Uiv *vtf
              S3 ered it. It is intended only to light,
              9 our own path.'
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030431/1919-09-09/ed-1/?sp=8&amp;q=league+of+nations&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.189,-0.291,1.378,1.378,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              "Will the President deny that the
              "League of Nations gives the supervision.
              of our trade In arms to the league, while
              the Constltutldn gives It to Congress?
              "Is It not true that the covenant of
              the league provides that when the else
              of the army nnd navy has been fixed as
              provided under it they cannot be In
              creased without the consent of the
              league, while the Constitution gives Con
              gress the absolute power to raise armies
              and navies?
              "It Is not true that the covenant
              Obligates us to defend the territorial In
              tegrity Of all of the proposed members
              of the league? How can we defend their
              territorial integrity without war? What
              voice would -our people have In such a
              war, provided for In advance by the
              League of -Nations, If we are to keep our
              obligations under tho league?
              "Is It not truo that every question
              likely to lead to a rupture Is to be de
              cided by the league, and we are bound
              to obey ita decisions? Does not this In
              volve every interest of the United Stated
              without exception? In this decision,
              dees not Great Britain with her colonies
              have six votes In the body of delegates
              while the United Stntes has only one?
              Why should Great Britain havo six
              tlmjfs as many votes as the United
              BtalcB? And why should Iledjaz or
              Haiti or Liberia have each as many
              votes as the United States?
              "The President says limitation of
              armaments cannot be Obtained without
              the League of Nations. Is that so? If
              It Is so, how Is it that we have limitation
              of armaments between the United States
              and Canada without a League of Na
              tions? Does not the President himself
              ray that' disarmament can only come by
              International conference? Cannot we
              have International conferences without a
              League 'of Nations? Ho says there Is an
              International agreement for disarmament
              In the, covenant or the League of Na
              tlpns. Thero Is no such agreement
              t.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86076241/1918-11-29/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=league+of+nations</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              To Senator Reed of Missouri belongs the distinction of discover
              ing in the proposed League of Nations to Enforce Peace a treasonable
              conspiracy against the honor and interests of the United States. Such
              a league, he says, would involve us in every European quarrel; it
              would expose the president to the cabals of raonarchs, all closely re
              lated; it would necessarily result in the creation of an international
              army powerful enough to coerce any nation, the United states in
              eluded, of course, which in time might be commanded by a German
              field marshal, and in, its councils, eacn nation voting as a unit, this
              mighty republic would have no more influence than Hayti or Liberia.
              If the senator can-be made to understand that the League of
              Nations is not altogether a hallucination but a practical conception of
              international action which is soberly indorsed by many far-seeing
              men, he will realize that every one of his objections has been or will
              be answered, the New-York World declares. We hesitate to assume
              that Mr. Reed has intentionally misrepresented the plan which he as
              sails, but, plainly enough, he is lll-inrormed as to its inspiration and
              purpose.
              The war now ending has shown that never again can wre ignore
              European quarrels. We did our best some people thought our worst
              --to keep out of this one, and failed. The nations of the earth are
              too closely associated to hope ever again to be disinterested observers
              of war between important belligerents. In that role we suffered
              many wrongs and humiliations, and the-neutrality of such states as
              Holland, Norway and Denmark has been hardly less costly than war.
              A League of Nations has always beenpredicated upon the dls
              appearance of autoeracyy-which has been the parent of aggresion
              and strife. The last of the autocrats has gone, and the monarchs of
              whom Mr. Reed stands in such fear have less actual power than the
              governor of an American commonwealth.
              How a League of Nations would arrive at its conclusions and en
              force them against offenders has not yet been worked out, but we
              think it must be.taken for granted that before such an organization
              can be effected the purpose of the world to maintain peace and jus
              tice will be made known beyond a peradventure, and that, with that
              common aim once established, the method by which it is to be at
              tained will be reached without much difficulty. Afterall, it is noth
              ing but democratic self-government on a large scale, j
              Inother words, a League of Nations presupposes a membership
              of free and civilized and not enslaved and savage nations. It must
              rest also to some extent upon mutual respect and confidence. To be
              effective it must mckide every considerable nation. Its success will
              depend more upon the principles of its members than upon any meas
              ures of disarmament, although it is expected, of course, that in time
              the great war machines ot the present day will be seen no more.
              Such a League of Nations as most people have in mind wHl not
              execute its decrees with the sword, and so Mr. Reed's hideous dream
              that a German may in time lead an overpowering international force
              against the United States falls to the ground. Its' discipline in the
              first instance will be commercial and financial. No unruly govern
              ment can long survive an international boycott. None but unruly
              peoples need fear anything more drastic than that.
              A Leagiie of Nations to Enforce Peace should be no more ter
              rible to well-disposed nations than the rule of law to communities
              long subject to assassins, mobs and lynchers. It would seem that this
              truth might appeal to Mr. Reed as a distinguished member of the
              bar, even if he were not a senator of the United States.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84001718/1920-10-29/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=league+of+nations&amp;r=-1.137,-0.042,3.274,1.482,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Under the name of "mandates” of
              the League of Nations, a military gov
              ernment is being imposed upon Meso
              potamia and Syria. It may be neces
              sary; but it is neither necessary nor
              proper that the United States shall
              become a party to it. Whether we
              shall or not not may be finally deter
              mined by the senate, and by a single
              vote in the senate.
              The Republican party proposes to
              maintain those separate fortunes for
              which our fathers fought. America
              independence of Europe has meant
              much for the world as well as for
              ourselves, and its sacrifice would be
              a sacrifice for all mankind as well
              ns for ourselves.
              ~lf disarmament can be brought
              about it will be by friendly agreement,
              as with Canada, and not by a military
              league, as established at Paris.
              If the future peace of the world
              is to encouraged, it will be by the
              eonditieation of international law and
              the establishment of a court of law
              judges, to which the nations, in a free
              association will submit disputes.
              Only war will come from the setting
              up a centralized military power,
              which by its assembly, exercising, as
              the President has said, "the major
              forces of mankind." will subject the
              world to an unscrupulous and irre
              sponsible politicial and military des
              potism.
              Thi! Democratic party will deny
              that such a power will be unscroupu
              lous or despotic. The history of the
              world proves that It will be.
              The safeguard of the nation Is the
              election of u senate pledged to sup
              port our Constitution, or interests,
              and our American policies of peace
              and friendship with all nations and
              governmental union with none. We
              have fought four wars with Eunropean
              nations to prevent the control of
              American affairs by Europe, and won
              them all. It is certain that if the
              League of Nations had been in exist
              ence we would never have gained our
              independence. Do not let us now
              commit the supreme folly an dthe “su
              preme sacrifice” of voluntarily sur
              rendering the independence and sepa
              rate station in the world which we
              have won.—Miles Poindexter.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86076241/1920-10-08/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=league+of+nations&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.29,-0.079,1.579,1.579,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Governor Cox states that as president he will bring the League
              of Nations before the senate at the tirst opportunity for ratification
              with any helpful reservations that are advanced.
              Senator Harding states that the League of Nations is dead, that
              he is against it and so the issue is clearly denned.
              In the event of the election of Governor Cox the first official act
              he performs will be to enter the United States in the League of Na
              tions and to cause this nation to assume its rightful place in the pro
              gress and advancement of the world. He will bring about that for
              which the American soldiers went overseas the elimination of wars
              in the future through the agreement of the nations of the world act
              ing in harmony through the League of Nations.
              Senator Harding offers no substitute. He is -boldly, unutter
              ably against the League of Nations.
              This is the situation presenting itself in this campaign. Will
              the American people vote for Cox and the League of Nations or will
              they follow blindly a candidate who offers them nothing tangible
              to prevent future devastating wars?
          </text>
      </result>

    </results>
  </topic>
  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-chinese-exclusion-act</id>
    <results>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85053040/1882-05-13/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Bill+bill+Chinese+signed&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.297,-0.08,1.594,1.594,0</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            The Chinese Bill.
            The bill signed by the President on the
            8th inst., entitled "An act to execute cer
            tain treutv stipulations relating to Chinese,"
            provides In the first section for the suspen
            sion of the immigration of Chinese laborers
            to the United States for a period of ten
            years, counting from the expiration of
            ninety days after the passage of the act,
            that is for to years from the 30th dav of
            July 1882. The second section provides
            lor" tiie punishment of masters of vessels
            who shall land in the U. S-, Chinese labor
            ers in violation of section first, bv u fine of
            $500 for each immigrant and imprisonment
            not exceeding one year. Section third pro
            vides tor certificates of identity tor Chinese
            laborers now in the country, who may
            wish to visit China and return. Section
            twelve makes it the duty of the President
            of tiie United States to cause to be removed
            to tiie place from whence they came, and
            at the cost of the United States every Chi
            nese person who shall have unlawfully en
            tered this country by land or water, after
            being brought before some justice, judge or
            commissioner of a court of tiie United
            States. Section thirteen exempts diplo
            matic and other officers of tin; Chinese
            Government and their body and .musehold
            servants from the provisions of the act.
            The two following sections are the ones
            against which so much opposition lias been
            shown by Republican Congressmen.
            Section' 14. That hereafter no State
            court or court of the United States shall ad
            mit Chinese to citizenship; and all laws in
            conflict with this act are repealed.
            Section- 15. That tiie words "Chinese
            Laborei s" wherever used in this act shall
            be constructed to mean both skilled and un
            skilled laborers and Chinese employ ed in
            mining.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1901-11-22/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Act+act+Chinese+Exclusion+exclusion</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            CHINESE EXCLUSION CONVENTION OPENS
            FIGHT IN DEFENSE OF AMERICAN LABOR
            PRESIDENT WILL URGE RE-ENACTMENT OF EXCLUSION LAW.
            D. C, Nov. 21, 1901. Hon. James D. Phelan, San Francisco, Cal.; I have seen the President. I have the best authority for saying that he will not only recom
            mend in his message the re-enactment of the Geary law, but will go further and urge that it be made stronger. J, c. NEEDHAM.
            CHINESE QUESTION ONE OF" RACE
            TyTy E are the warders of the Golden Gate; we must stand
            y y here forever in the pathway of the Orient, and if there
            is any danger or trial it is for us to sound the alarm.
            I regard the Chinese question as a race question. I regard
            it as an international question; and above and over all, a
            question involving the preservation of our civilisation. The State
            of California, with its sezrn hundred miles of seaboard facing
            the Orient, is entitled to speak on this question for tlie people of
            the United States. Excerpt from Mayor James D. Phelan' s ad
            dress at the Chinese Exclusion Convention.
            Leading Citizens Gather to Urge
            Re-enactment of the
            Geary Law.
            IT was a distinctly representative
            gathering of business, professional
            and laboring men that packed Metro
            politan Temple yesterday afternoon
            when Mayor Phelan called the Chi
            nese Exclusion Convention to order.
            Xearly every seat in the large auditorium
            •was taken, the lower floor being devoted
            to the use of the delegates from all parts
            of California, while the gallery was given
            up to the general public. All present
            seemed to be animated by one impulse,
            that of doing their utmost to secure the
            re-enactment of the Chinese exclusion act
            and thereby prevent the threatened In
            vasion of Mongol horclee to the peril and
            degradation of American labor.
            The gathering was of that character
            which lends weight to any public move
            ment and the conclusions of which are ac
            corded respectful consideration In legisla
            tive halls. The convention was not the
            outgrowth of political or partisan senti
            ment, but of the fear of the people of the
            State that the danger which menaces
            their advancement and prosperity might,
            unless strong measures were taken, be
            actually realized. In order that the peo
            ple of the East might understand how
            the communities on the "Western confines
            of the continent feel concerning the un
            restricted immigration of Chinese into
            their midst, the convention was decided
            upon, and it is needless to say that the
            memorial which is to be adopted to-day
            will prove to be an unanswerable argu
            ment to those of the East, who, without
            the slightest knowledge of the blight-
            Borne characteristics of the Chinese, have
            df-clared open sympathy for the coolie
            hordes which are only awaiting the ex
            piration of the exclusion act in May next
            SENATOR PERKINS WOULD CO FURTHER.
            /T is our people who pay the taxes that have built up our splendid institutions, and we should
            draw the line furtJter, only this is not the time nor occasion. I would permit no one to come into
            this country unless he felt as he approaches these shores as Moses did when he approached the
            burning bush that he stood upon sacred ground; and the voice coming out of that bush from the
            American people is "Unless you love freedom, unless you believe in republican institutions, unless you
            believe in the free public schools, you cannot come into this country." Excerpt from Senator Perkins'
            address before the Chinese Exclusion Convention.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1901-11-23/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=Chinese+CHINESE+exclusion+EXCLUSION+Exclusion&amp;r=-1.148,-0.005,3.296,1.492,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              THE Chinese Exclusion Convention
              completed its labor? yesterday
              after the adoption of one of the
              most important as well as vipor
              ous memorials on the Chinese
              question ever addressed to the
              President and Congress of the United
              Elates. The attitude of the people of Cal
              ifornia and of the entire Pacific Coast to
              ward the problem of unrestricted immi
              gration of Asiatics to these shores as rep
              resented in the convention was distinctly
              outlined, and its language cannot fail to
              he understood in the East as being the
              Fpontaneous outburst of a united people
              n the imposition upon them i f a
              grievous wrong.
              The delegates gathered in force yester
              day morning and listened with enthusi
              asm to many speakers. Only one theme
              was discuss-ei, only one idea advanced,
              namely, unalterable resistance to the pro
              ject of unrestricted Chinese immigration
              to America. Tie danger of a Mongolian
              invasion In the event of the refusal of
              :ess to re-enact the exclusion law
              wae pointed out in forceful language by
              all the speakers. The delegates choc-reel
              heartily at every patriotic sentiment
              voiced by the orators, and particularly
              when the necessity o* protecting Ameri
              can labor against foreign competition was
              urged. The members of the convention
              .6howed by their zeal t^at they were in
              accord with the speakers, whose senti
              ments they cordially indo-f>ed.
              The report of the comir.ittee on perma
              nent organization was tae first matter
              to engage the attention of the delegates
              et the morning session. The recommen
              dation that the temporary officers be
              made permanent was adopted amid
              cheers. It was expected that the memo
              l rial committee would be abl* to file its
              report, but the announcement by Chair
              man Geary that further time was re-
              Quired by the cotimittee resulted in the
              desired action beltg taken. There being
              sm> definite bufiinesi before the convention,
              The San Francisco Call.
              speechmaking was indulged in. Assistant
              Tnii^rj States District Attorney Duncan
              E. McKinlay was introduced by the chair,
              and that gentleman delivered an able ad
              dress in which he reviewed the Chinese
              question from the standpoint of the Dis
              trict Attorney's office. The legal aspects
              of the issue were capably presented, the
              peakcr's remarks at times evoking
              hearty applause. So favorably did he im
              press his hearers that at the close of his
              speech he was honored by a Tote of
              thanks for his brilliant oratorical effort.
              The Rev. Dr. William Rader followed
              with a witty address, in which he re
              viewed the Chinese question from the
              standpoint of morality and religion. His
              allusions to the vices prevailing in San
              Francisco's Chinatown, and of their ef
              fect upon the whole community, were im
              pressively advanced, and his remark that
              the proper place in which to Christianize
              the Chinese was in China and not in this
              country, evoked cheers. The address
              was replete with statistical information,
              and it was listened to with profound in
              terest by all present.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1901-11-26/ed-1/?sp=12&amp;q=act+Chinese+exclusion&amp;r=-0.867,0.229,2.735,1.238,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              COMMISSIONERS ABE NAMED.
              Chairman Geary Appoints Men to
              Chinese Exclusion Committees.
              Thomas J. Geary, chairman of the Cali
              fornia Exclusion Convention, announces
              the following appointments:
              Commissioners of California to "Washington—
              Andrew Furuseth, ex-Governor James H. Budd,
              Truxton Beale, James D. Phelan and Edward
              J. Llvernash.
              Press committee— P. Bufflngton of the Jack
              son Republican. E. A. "Walcott of the Ex
              aminer John McNaueht of The Call, Edward
              F. Adams of the Chronicle, Charles punbar of
              the Santa Rosa. Press-Democrat.
              Additions to executive committee— A. Sbar
              boro George Stone, Jeremiah F. Sullivan,
              James H. Wllklns, Henry H. Taylor, Thomas
              F Barry, M. H. de Young, James H. O'Brien,
              Arthur G. Fisk. J. C. Kirkpatrick, George A.
              Ross. Eugene E. Schmitz, Ed Rosenberg. J. S.
              Parry, George H. Knight.
              VOTE ON CHINESE EXCLUSION.
              Merchants' Association Takes Boli of
              Members on Important Question.
              The returns from a vote of the mem
              bers of the Merchants' on
              questions pertaining to the Chinese ex
              clusion act are as follows:
              Do you favor the extension of the present
              Chinese exclusion act? Ayes, 425; noes, 208.
              Do you favor a modified Chinese exclusion
              act? Ayes, 243; noes, 376.
              Do you favor sending delegates from the
              Merchants' Association to the Chinese exclusion
              convention? Ayes. 638; noes, 91.
              Affirmative answers to No. 3, if pledged for
              Chinese exclusion act Ayes. 11; noes, 0.
              Affirmative answers to No. 3, if pledged
              against Chinese exclusion act Aye-, 7; noes, 0.
              Affirmative answers to No. 3, if pledged for
              modified Chinese exclusion act— Ayes, 5; noes, 0.
              Affirmative answers to No. 3, If pledged also
              for Japanese exclusion Ayes, 1; noes, 0.
              Parties desire matter to be left to board of
              directors' discretion— Ayes, 4; noes, 0.
              The delegates who were appointed by
              the Merchants' Association to the Chi
              nese Exclusipn Convention, are Prank J.
              Symmes, Marshal Hale and Andrew M.
              Davis.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/46032385/1901-12-06/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=act+Chinese+exclusion&amp;r=-0.286,0.087,1.588,0.719,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              The Yellow Peril.
              It will be necessary for the present congress
              to. take acjtion upon the Chinese exclusion act
              which expires by limitation May 24, 1902. The
              Kjansas City platform contained the following
              plank on the subject:
              We favor the continuance and strict en-
              forcement of the Chinese exclusion law and
              its application to the samo classes of all
              'Asiatic races.
              This plank was unanimously agreed upon by
              the platform committee, and there was no dissent
              from it among the delegates. It is to be expected,
              therefore, that the proposition to extend the
              Chinese exclusion act will receive the support of
              all the democrats in the house and senate. The
              editor of The Commoner received a letter a few
              days ago from a democrat who complained that
              the laboring men of the Pacific slope had ignored
              the. Chinese question in the last campaign and
              suggested that it would only be a merited punish
              ment if the republican party refused to extend the
              exclusion act. It is not unnatural that some
              resentment should be felt toward those who sup
              ported the republican party in spite of the dangers
              which republican supremacy involves, and yet no
              one can justify himself in either supporting a bad
              policy or in failing to protest against it merely be
              cause the policy would punish .some who ought to
              have exerted themselves to prevent ij:. That
              many of the republican leaders are in favor of a
              ..policy, Jfcat will flood the country with cheap
              Chinese labor, is true, and that an imperial policy
              tends to lend encouragement to the cheap labor
              proposition, is also true, but the failure of the
              laboring men' to see these dangers in advance
              would not justify .democrats in remaining quiet
              on this subject, although the republicans are in
              "power and are responsible for legislation.
              The Chinese question is one that effects the en
              tire country, not the Pacific Coast alone or the
              laboring men alone. It is true that the Pacific
              Coast would feel the evil effects of Chinese emigra
              tion first, and it is also true that the laboring men
              would come into immediate contact with oriental
              labor, but in its ultimate influence the subject
              touches all parts of the country and reaches all
              classes. The question is whether we are going to
              build up a strong, independent, upright and pa
              triotic people and develop a civilization that will
              exert a helpful influence on all the world, or
              whether we are going to be a greedy, grasping na
              tion, forgetful of high ideals and concerned only
              in the making of money.
              Chinese emigration is defended by two classes
              of people. First, by those, comparatively few in'
              number, who believe that universal brotherhood
              requires us to welcome to our shores all people of
              all lands. This is the sentimental argument ad
              vanced in favor of Chinese emigration. There Is
              no more reason why we should construe brother
              hood to require the admission of all people to our
              country than there is that we should construe
              brotherhood to require the dissolution of family
              ties. The family is a unit; it is the place where
              character and virtue and usefulness are developed,
              and from the family a good or evil influence ema
              nates. It is not necessary nor even wise that the
              family environment should be broken up or that
              ill who desire entrance should bet admitted to the
              family oircle. In a larger sense a nation is a
              family. It is the center for the cultivation of na
              tional character, national virtue and national use
              fulness. A nation is under no obligation to the
              outside world to admit any body or anything that
              would injuriously effect the national family; in
              fact it Is under obligation to itself not to do so.
              The influence of the United States will bo much
              more potent for good if we Temaln a homogeneous
              nation with all citizens in full sympathy with all
              other citizens. No distinct race like tho Chinese
              can come into this country without exciting a fric
              tion and a race prejudlco which will mako it moro
              difficult for us to exercise a wholesome influence
              upon the Chinese in China, not to speak of our in
              fluence on other nations.
              Let us educate tho Chinese who desire to learn
              of American institutions; let us offer courtesy and
              protection to those who come here to travel' and
              investigate, but it will not be of permanent benefit
              to either the Chinese or to us to Invite them to be
              come citizens or to permit them to labor here and
              carry the proceeds of their toil back to their own
              country.
              The second, and by far the larger class, em
              braces those who advocate Chinese emigration on
              the ground that it will furnish cheap labor for
              household- and factory work. There is no force In
              the argument that is made by some that it is diffi
              cult to secure girls to do housework. If domestic
              service is not popular as compared with other
              w.ork, it is because the pay is not sufficient to mako
              it attractive and the remedy lies in better wages.
              Labor can be secured for any and every honorable
              -position-when-the'i'4sufflcienfc-to'attratitr'
              and the demand for Chinese servants comes with
              poor grace from those who often spend on a sin
              gle social entertainment as much as a servant'3
              wages would amount to in an entire year. At this
              time When skilled and intelligent American labor
              is able to compete in foreign markets with the
              cheapest, labor of the world, it is absurd to talk
              about the necessity for cheap factory hands.
              The increase in Japanese Immigration, or rath
              er importation (for large numbers of them are
              brought for specific purposes) has been referredto
              in a former issue of The Commoner. IWwas there
              suggested that the Japanese government would
              doubtless, if asked to do so, place restrictions upon
              Japanese emigration that would make it unneces
              sary for us to deal with the subject by legislation.
              This matter should at once be brought to tho at
              tention of the Japanese authorities, and unles3
              sufficient and satisfactory action Is taken by the
              home government the Chinese exclusion act should
              be made broad enough to extend to Japanese of
              the same class.
              The subject of oriental emigration cannot be
              discussed without giving some consideration to
              the danger of cheap labor from the Philippine isl
              ands. It will soon be necessary to legislate on
              this subject. If the Filipinos are permitted to
              come here there is danger that the Philippine ques
              tion will become only second in aggravation lo
              the Chinese question. If, on the other hand, the
              Filipinos are prohibited from coming here (if a
              republic can prohibit the inhabitants of one part
              from visiting another part of the republic), will it
              not excite a just protest on the part of the Fili
              pinos? How can we excuse ourselves if we In
              sist upon opening the Philippine islands to the In
              vasion of American capital, American speculators,
              and American task-masters, and yet close our doors
              to those Filipinos who, driven from home, may
              seek an asylum here?
              TIio democratic party should take a strong
              and aggresslvo position on this question. It can
              afford to'oppoBO Chinese emigration and insist
              upon tho unity and homogoncousness of "oiir
              nation. It can afford to Insist that Japanese la
              borers shall be treated the samo as Chinese labor
              ers and excluded, by agreement with tho Japanese
              government if possible, by congressional legisla
              tion if necessary.
              The democratic leaders should further point
              out that the Philippine question involves tho samo
              menace to our country, and that as wo can neither
              afford to admit tho Filipinos nor yet mako a dis
              tinction between different parts of tho republic,
              we should at once declare our purposo to give the
              Filipinos independence as soon as a stable govern
              ment can be established.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1902-04-17/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=CHINESE+Chinese+exclusion+EXCLUSION</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              The Senate failed to substitute' the
              enacting clause 'of the House bill; for th'e
              Senate measure, so that the bill 'now! will
              go to the House as an "original measure
              and from a" parliamentary standpoint will
              have to he acted on and "treated the same
              as though- the I louse ;had not. passed a
              Chinese 'exclusion bill already.
              pThc vote' by which the substitute took
              the .place of the originalwas ayes 48 to
              noes 33. Once the substitution had been
              made air the Senators joined in its sup
              port, with the single^ exception of Hoar,
              the substitute being passed,. 76 to 1. The
              friends of the^ 1 substitute .'showed their
              strength throughout the voting on amend
              ments .that preceded final action and; sue-,
              ceeded in preventing any 'material change
              in' its features. Some minor, conditions
              were made, admitting Chinese persons
              connected with national expositions^ arid
              providing for certiflcates\of Identification
              of /Chinese l in our insular, possessions.
              Otherwise, 'however, the. substitute was
              adopted substantially in "the 'form thit
              Platt presented it.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn87065462/1905-06-21/ed-1/?sp=7&amp;q=Act+Chinese+Exclusion&amp;r=-0.236,0.666,0.858,0.389,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              President Roosevelt is reported
              to be very indignant because the
              Chinese Exclusion Act is being
              vigorously enforced, says the New
              York American.
              n..ia a. T 1 L i
              irresiueui jiuuBe veiii uugui uui
              to complain of vigor, because he is
              the national exponent of the stren-
              .nous life.
              h Also, President Roosevelt has
              nnaAil a a favftrinrr thn vifnrnriR An-
              j o
              forcemeat, of all laws regardless of
              the feelings and interests of indi
              viduals. There is no Iaw on the statute
              books of the United tates more
              Important to the wellbeing of the
              citizens of this conchy than the
              Chinese Exclusion Act.
              Despite the great vigilance of
              the officials, the law is constantly
              being eluded and broken even to
              day. It has been found almost impos
              sible to protect the two thousand
              miles on the Pacific Coast frontier
              against the invasion1 of Chinese,
              j Trho employ every device known
              to human ingenuity to pass the
              Hues.
              Before President Roosevelt gets
              .r.Jignact about the vigorous en
              forcement of the Chinese Exclu
              sion Act, he might better consult
              with the Federal judges andoffi
              Jala of Pacific Coast ports.,
              Juflga Morrow, of San Francis
              co, for instance,' could tell him
              that perjury, forgery of firtiS
              stes, forgery of photographs and
              Vernation of purgery are nni
              cr?:il in Chinese cases.
              Iumigrant Commissioner North
              culi tell him that, despite the tit
              nost precautions, cm Chinese la
              ulatituteil for another, and that
              rca now tl.rre is trlcrethade
              itrscct tLs exar:.:Eitica cf r.any
              i wLcra CLir- af t,!avP3
              ira L:en Ban:!: I i. '.3 W.i caun-
              11.2 CLiiese lit-: i Act b
              c 1 1
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84024827/1905-06-30/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=ACT+act+Chinese+CHINESE+exclusion+EXCLUSION&amp;r=-0.163,0.262,1.084,0.491,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              THE CHINESE
              EXCLUSION ACT.
              One of the big questions which is
              agitating thit country at tho present
              time is the Chinese exclusion act, and
              the effect its rigid enforcement has
              now and may have in the future, on
              American commerce and trade in
              China. The exportation of cotton and
              cotton goods to China has grov-n from
              almost nothing to $40,000,000 in a few
              yca-s. Other lines of exports to the
              celestial kingdom have shown very
              large gams. The American manufac
              turer is clamoring tor an open door
              to the trade of China. The American
              manufacturer has always been solf-
              ifsh and in most instances, been ready
              to sacrifice the good of the people to
              his own profit and selfish ends. It
              matters little to the manufacturer of
              cotton goods in New England or the
              south if the Pacific coast and adja
              cent territory is overrun with cheap
              Chinese coolies, the lowest strata of
              Chinese life. 5f he can find a ready
              and a profitable market for a few
              more millions of dollars of cotton
              goods and other products of his shops.
              7"he cry for more liberal immigration
              Jiws for the Chinese comes wholly
              Irom the manufacturers. Tne people
              of the Pacific coast don't want the
              aan at any price. He is a men-
              ace to this country and his very pres
              ence exerts a contaminating in
              fluence. It is impossible for him to
              amalgamate with the people of this
              country. He can not become a citizen
              and ho has no desire to make this
              land of the free his home and reside
              here permanently. Personally he Is
              as objectionable as tho negro of the
              J south and if we must have cheap labor
              1 let us give the negro a chance. "We
              lave him with us and while he is not
              .as skillful as the Chinaman or as In
              dustrious, he Is by far the best cheap
              laborer in the world.
              The Chinese exclusion act has been
              in operation for more than twenty
              years. At tho time of its passage a
              perfect horde of orientals were
              streaming Into this country, over
              running the Pacific coast states, and
              drifting far back into the interior. The
              exclusion act stopped this unholy in
              vasion at once and the flow of China
              men began to go the other way. There
              were at that time more than a quar
              ter of a million Chinamen In the
              "United States. During these twenty
              years this number has been on the
              gradual decline. Death has thinned
              tho ranks of the yellow skinned sons
              of the east and a large proportion of
              the Chinamen who were in this coun
              try have made their "stake" and re
              turned to China to remain. In San
              Francisco. Los Angeles, Portland and
              Seattle the gradual decrease in the
              number of Chinese has been most
              notable. It is doubtful if at the pros
              sent time there are 50,000 Chinese in
              the entire country, and the country
              will be infinitely better off when
              these, too, "have folded their tents,
              like the Arab, and silently stolen
              away."
              The manufacturers, for years, have
              kept an outrageous tariff on all
              classes of manufactured goods by
              their cry of "protection to American
              labor," and they have filtched mill
              ions of dollars from the pockets of
              the people under the guise of a tariff
              to enrich their own. It matters not
              to them how heavy the burden on
              the shoulders of the people, just so
              they get their pound of flesh. Now
              they wo ild throw wide open the doors
              to the Chinese in order to get a few
              more dollars of trade.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85042462/1905-07-21/ed-1/?sp=9&amp;q=Chinese+CHINESE+Exclusion+EXCLUSION+exclusion</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              CHINESE SCORES
              EXCLUSION LAW
              OPPOSING THINKERS IN A
              HEATED DEBATE
              'UNJUST/ SAYS NG POON CHEW
              Noted Oriental and Rev. William
              Rader of San Francisco Argue
              Right of Exclusion
              Acts 7
              "Chinese exclusion as a measure of
              protection for, American labor Is a fal
              lacy. American labor needs no protec
              tion and the anti-Chinese crusade
              amounts to nothing more than the op
              pression of a set of foreigners without
              votes by, a set of foreigners with the
              voting power."
              jvNg Poon Chew, a noted San Francis
              co editor, was angry at the wrongs done
              his people and hurled his defiance at
              Rev. William Rader. In thel^ great de,
              bate before the Venice assembly last
              night. if"
              *j'Ng Poon Chew had' the negative side
              ;of^ the question,: "Resolved, that Chl
              'nese exclusion Is reasonable and neces
              sary, while Rev. William. Rader, also
              of San Francisco, upheld the offtrma
              ,'tlve.yW
              'As the first affirmative Rev. Rader
              the subject, outlined the ex-
              I lstlng conditions and the stand taken
              ;by T the present^admlnlstratlon.
              Rev. Mr. Rader Argues
              i-^ln'.part Rev. Rader said: "The exclu
              sion^ of the Chinese la not urged upon
              the .'grounds of prejudice. We have -no
              [objection to their religion. Joss is 'as
              free as "Jesus. No apology Is made for
              the 111 treatment of the exempt classes,
              ;but T ;l;'stand ..with i the. administration
              when It declares for coolie exclusion.
              A'V.'The question Is not a sentimental
              one. It is a question of national mean-
              Ing, f. We, should have uniform emigra
              tion, laws. More foreigners landed on
              our shores last year than there are peo
              ple* In Los 'Angeles and San Francisco;
              Sentiment' goes down before such facts.
              -"'"I maintain that it is within the.prov
              lnce of the state, to restrict' emigration
              If It so desires: Exclusion is practiced
              In; nature, in very home..,-;
              l.' "Chinese exclusion is reasonable and
              necessary for at least two great rea
              sons. .v
              "First, because of the effect that un
              restricted Immigration would have upon
              our civilization.: America cannot digest
              China. Chinese do not j assimilate: ■My
              opponent— an -exception— proves^., the
              rule.'| There is not another Chinaman in
              California who has reached the posl
              !tlon|thls -.man has j reached. We can
              make servants of the Chinese but not
              citizens and soldiers. They bring with
              ,lAein"; customs and vices which: add to
              bur disorders. They bring sanitary con
              ditions", which are a menace to the pub
              lic health.; In San' Francisco there have
              been 1 more deaths, ln' the Chinese quar
              ter] than"' In -the city 'proper. Li.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86063381/1906-01-10/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=act+Chinese+exclusion&amp;r=-0.264,0.404,1.184,0.536,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              EXCLUSION LAW IS VALID
              COURT OF APPEALS DECLARES
              CONGRESS HAD POWER TO
              EXTEND STATUTE.
              Cincinnati, Jan. 10.The case of
              Hong Wing against the United States,
              involving the Chinese exclusion act,
              was decided in favor of the United
              States circuit court of appeals in this
              city, the court holding that the act of
              .April 7, 1904, continued the exclusion
              act in full force, congress haying full
              potyer to dp so.
              Hong Wing is one of six Chinamen
              who had been ordered deported under
              the provisions of the Chinese exclu
              sion act and the cases being identical
              the one decision will apply to all six.
              Attorneys for the applicant main
              tained that the exclusion act was void
              and that their clients eould not be de
              ported.
              The decision was announced by
              Judge Richards, who said that the
              main point presented to the court was
              whether the act of April 7, 1904, con
              tinued the Chinese exclusion act in
              force and the court was satisfied that
              it did do so without reference to any
              existing treaties or regulations. The
              act was passed in view of the treaty
              expiring and it had continued the pro
              visions of the treaty. Congress has
              the power to modify, reject or concur
              in treaties and it had done what was
              wholly within its power in passing this
              act. The decision of the lower court
              was, therefore, sustained and the ap
              peal dismissed. '-..hffam
          </text>
      </result>
      <!-- five additional -->
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84036162/1904-08-25/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=chinese+exclusion+act&amp;r=-0.052,0.327,1.353,0.613,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86076200/1901-08-03/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=chinese+exclusion+act&amp;r=0.053,0.18,0.768,0.348,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              CHINESE EXCLUSION.
              Miners' I nlon Petition* tor
              enactment of the Present tow.
              The Sentinel publisher below a lettei
              from a oommittee of th# Tosoarors
              Miners' Union together with a petition
              which it to be presented to Congrast
              asking the re-enactment of the Chinese
              Exclusion Act. The petition should be
              generally signed as the question ia one
              which appeals to the people of th ie
              State. The more against Chinese immi
              gration has been started in the right
              quarter—by the labor unions—aa the
              laboring people will be the greatest suf
              ferers ahonld the Chinese be permitted
              to again invade this country
              To the Kdltor of the Bxstinxl:
              The within petition will in a measure
              explain itself. The Chinese Exclusion
              Aot will expire by limitation in May,
              1902. As labor it the first to feel the
              evil effects of the importation of cheap
              labor and degraded workers, organized
              labor baa decided to appeal, through
              petition, to the people for a re-enact
              ment of the Chinese Exclusion Act, with
              mendments that appear in the petition.
              We do not deem it necessary to argue
              the question with the people of Nevada,
              for we think they folly understand the
              evils of Asiatio immigration and only
              want the opportunity presented to act.
              lienee we would ask you to be kind
              enough to give our letter and petition
              apace in your valuable paper to the end
              that the people may folly understand
              the purport of the petition when pre
              sented to them for signature. This com
              mittee will send petitions to every post
              office in Elko, Eureka, Lander and Hum
              boldt counties. From this you will see
              that our work ia large, but the stake
              played for—the Amerioan home—it
              worth it. Wa would respectfully urge
              every mao and women to act promptly;
              delays are dangerous. Any assistance
              through your valuable paper will be ap
              preciated.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn99062049/1905-07-14/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=chinese+exclusion+act&amp;r=-1.255,-0.08,3.51,1.592,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85047211/1905-03-01/ed-1/?sp=7&amp;q=chinese+exclusion+act&amp;r=0.109,0.413,1.375,0.624,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83025308/1892-01-30/ed-1/?sp=5&amp;q=chinese+exclusion+act</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Numesaous li gned' Petit ia. Asbklnll Con
              srqps to Pasil a stringent ExclusIon
              Act Agattist the, lioallants.
              The meeting at Assembly hall last night
              to discuss the 'Cbloese question was well
              attended by workingmen of Helena, J, E.
              Boncher presided and J. Y. Bennett was
              secretary, Chairman Boucher stated that
              all were no doubt aware that the Chinese
              exclusion act expired in May, and that a
              measure would be introduced in congress
              to continue the restriction. "It is a matter
              of interest to us and to the business men of
              Helena," bhe said. "I am surprised that
              there are not more basiness men present,
              But because there are eot more of them is
              no reason why we should not express our
              opinions."
              L i. Glidea said the meeting had been
              called by him to take action on the peti
              tions to congress for the exclusion of the
              Chinese, and for the election of senators by
              the direct vote of the people, both of which
              were suggeted by T. V. Powderly. The seo
              retary stated that he had petitions on the
              Chinese question prepared for the signa
              tures of those present and for other work
              ingmen's organizations. It was decided to
              allow five minutes to each man to talk on
              the subject. As this was announced one mani
              present began a rambling speech about the
              uselessness of the Chinese to the mer
              chants, the doctors and the real estate men,
              and was proceeding to state that China had
              44,000,000 people and the United States but
              17,000,000, when the bhairman called him
              down with the remark that this was a
              meeting to discuss a serious problem, and
              not a "josh." The culprit took his seat,
              and, the discussion was taken up in a seri
              ons strdin.
              John Finn suggested that the working
              men would have to come out and let it be
              known to the politicians that whoever was
              not on their side could not get thir votes.
              F. A. Adrian said they could nothing un
              less they all stood together and refused to
              patronize the Chinamen or those who em
              ployed them.
              Adolf Halest thought the question a grave
              one, not only because the Chinaman worked
              for less than a white person, but because
              what money these people got was with
              drawn from the already inadequate circulr
              tion and taken back to their native land.
              Besides that there were the vices the Chi
              nrmen brought here, such as the opium
              habit. While it was impossible to get rid
              of all the Chinamen now here, it would be
              well to keep others from comine. Those
              now here would soon die out. He said the
              working people had to patronize the Chi
              namen for their garden truck because no
              white man raised any, but that would not
              be enough to keep them here.
              Chairman Boncher said the solution of
              the problem was a difficult one. It might
              do to take the almost unprecedented step
              of sending all the Chinamen back, but as
              that was well nigh impossible, the next
              great question was how to mitigate the
              evil and reduce it to the minimum. The
              exclusion -act did nrot remedy the disease.
              it was not heroic enough. It was wonder
              ful how, when congress passed a law, it was
              so easy to evade it. The people of the
              United States were most considerate of
              evil doers. It would seem that when any
              great wrong was committed it was neces
              sary for a certain class of people to get out
              and roar, and all the others called them
              agitators. Perhaps Dennis Kearney was an
              agitator, but he had a kick. No attention
              was paid to him, but when the trouble be
              gan to effect the upper classes, then congress
              took action. There were certain stores on
              Broadway occupied by Chinamen as mer
              chants. If the Chinman ever vacated the
              places the stores could never be rented to a
              white man for the same sum. That had
              been found out in Portland and San Fran
              oisco. But the Helena business men knew
              it all; they would not learn by experience.
              When the merchants began to feel the effect
              of the presence of the Chinese then the
              legislators would act. He feared they never
              would act on the appeal of the workingmen.
              "I he only way I see is to pass an exclusion
              not that will last forever." he continued.
              "We must say to our legislators that this is
              the one thing we insist upon. The Knights
              of Labor have a clause in. their declaration
              of principles that no creed or color shall be
              prohibited from being members. The same
              is found in the constitution of the United
              Statee. Yet Jefferson and the other fram
              ers of the constitution never meant a lot of
              vampires and bloodsuckers should be ad
              mnitted who come because we have some
              thing they want, aeni who, when they get
              it, go back home to enjoy it. Our only way
              is to impress on the minds of the people
              who are in office and those who want to get
              there, that their present and further safety
              depends on the passage of an exclusion act
              that will last forever."
              When the petition to congress was being
              passed around for signatures Mr. Gildea
              suggested taking up the senatorial question,
              but Michael Corbett thought that it would
              be bad policy to drop the Chinese matter at
              this point. He favored continuing to hold
              the meetines, but in a larger place. He
              also suggested withdrawing all patronage
              from the Chinamen. The quickest way to
              get rid of them is to lot them alone, Mr.
              Gildea said the Chinese question had been
              effectually disposed of so far as the present
              meeting was concerned. The question of
              electing senators by direct vote of the peo
              ple was eof as great, if not greater import
              ance than the Chinese question. The
              Chinese exclusion noact had been in force ten
              years, but it was a prohibition that did not
              prohibit. The other question was one of
              bringing the senato s closer to the people,
              where they conld,bo dealt with better and dic
              tated to in stronger terms than they could
              be now. Chairman Bouocher wanted
              another and a larger meeting with the
              business men present. liecretary Bennett
              did not have much faith in the business
              men attending. "As an example of their
              duplicity, or policy," he said, "you will re
              member that the council unanimously
              passed anti-Chinese resolutions. Four of
              ths men who voted for them employ China
              men in their houses. One told me it was
              because better service could be had from
              the Chinamen. The other said he would
              talk about it when the Burlingame treaty
              was rescinded." Mr. Gildea then moved to
              take up the senatorial question.
          </text>
      </result>
    </results>
  </topic>
  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-ping-pong-craze</id>
    <results>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1900-12-23/ed-1/?sp=29&amp;q=TABLE+TENNIS&amp;r=-1.337,-0.016,3.674,1.667,0</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            TABLE TENNIS.
            HI'LKS OF TLAY FOR THE NKW INIM>OR
            GAME. AI^SO CALLED POMPOM."
            Table tennis is the name of a new game which
            was introduced in England a short time ago.
            and has already become one of the most popu
            lar of indoor amusements. It is the came
            of lawn tennis in miniature, played on an or
            dinary dining table. The net is a tiny one, made
            of gauxe stretched between two uprights, which
            rest on a bar laid across the table. The balls
            are made of the thinnest kind of pyroxyline ma
            terial, and are consequently very light. The
            racquet has a slender handle and a blade with
            a frame about one-half inch thick, which Is cov
            ered on both sides with thin drumhead Material.
            The play and counting are practically the satnas in lawn tennis, but, according to the rules,
            '•the player serving must not put his racquet
            over the table nor have it above his wrist." That
            is, he must serve underhand and never over
            hand, but after service he may hit the ball as he
            likes, but he most not volley.
            The contact of the light ball with the drum
            head racquet produces a pleasant sound, and
            because of this sound th(» game received the
            name "pompom."
            Among the rules for playing the game are the
            following:
            No faults are allowed: if a fault is served.
            that is, the ball does not go over the net or goes
            off the table without touching the opposite side
            to the server, a |M>int is counted to the non
            server.
            If the net is touched by the l»all. and the ball
            goes over, and otherwise the service is correct,
            it is a let. and counU nothing to either side.
            If a volley is taken a point is counted against
            the person roUeytas-
            I.WSHOUM.'S I'Ehl.F.li WrHsTOll.
            THK lU:M.\KK.\ItI.K POtnCDKB "I" A IJR" -I KS*l-
            L.ISII Hul SK
            From The London Chronicle.
            Though he is one of the richest nea in Par
            liament, and has a house in Park Lane worth
            a fabulous sum, the new Foreign Secretary is,
            or ought to be. a man of stron human sympa
            thies. He owes his title and estates to a pedler.
            who was so poor that he lived in Paris for
            three weeks entirely on walnuts. Managing to
            earn an honest penny, he took out a patent for a
            letter copying machine, wrote on art and sci
            ence, practised chemistry and physics, sum
            moned the first meeting of the Royal Society at
            his lodgings, was appointed an army physician,
            invented a double bottomed ship to sail against
            wind and tide, founded iron works and opened
            l^ad mines, began a fishery and timber trade,
            and left a fortune to his sons. Such was the
            founder of the house of Lansdowne.
            Whether his podl^r ancestor's will has influ
            enced lAird Lansdowne in taking the Foreign
            Secretaryship or not we do not know, but in a
            remarkable will thai he Jeft behind the founder
            of the house conjured all his successors to "labor
            in public works" at their peril. "As for legacies
            for the poor." said the testator. "I am at a
            stand; as for beggars trade and election. I
            give them nothins: as for impotents by the hand
            of God. the public ought to maintain them; as
            for those who have been bred t.> no calling nor
            estate, they should be put upon their kindred;
            wherefore I am contented that I have
            assisted all my poor relations, and put many
            into a way of fretting their own bread; have la
            bored in public works, and by inventions have
            sought out r.-al objects of charity, and 1 do
            hereby conjure all who partake of my estate,
            from time to time, to do the same at their peril.
            Nevertheless, to answer custom, and to take the
            -idler side, I give £38 to the most wanting of the
            parish wherein I die."
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
	    <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1902-01-05/ed-1/?sp=26&amp;q=PING-PONG</id>
	    <rel>1</rel>
	    <text>
            AN ABSORBING HEW INDOOR GAITS
            WHICH HAS ATTAINED GREAT
            POPULARITY IN LONDON;
            The three men who occupied the studio flat
            were having their quiet end-afternoon srnoks
            together. There was the artist, w hose hair haj
            turned gray after long years of painting an*
            black and white doings; the youth who, fcesi
            from art school, was just making a start, and
            the man of business, who was the saving clause
            of the combination. He put up the money wh»3
            black and whites would not sell and the youths
            checks from home were delayed In the mails.
            "I wish people would find something new wia
            which to entertain us, said the man of buij.
            ness, in a bored tone.
            "New Year is coming," chirped the youth, aa
            obvious statement, setir.g that Christmas «xj
            just one day past. "Perhaps Santa Claus tLpgti
            off' the dear girls to a new game."
            There*! nothing new under the sun. Billy*
            said the •Id artist. "If taert was I'd draw it jj
            hurry."
            Then there came a knock on the door, and a
            messenger appeared with a dainty note. Billy
            grasped it hastily. Billy was in love.
            "It's addressed to all of us," he said, with di*.
            appointment.
            "All the more reason you should hurry up aaj
            lead it,"' commanded the man of business.
            "It's from Harriet," he murmured, as he read
            it to himself.
            "Head out loud, uli>.t"" commanded one of the
            older men.
            "Won't you ccme up to-morrow night and
            play ping-pong." read Billy. "Now, what is
            ping-pong?"
            "Search me?" remarked the one who was nut
            artistic, except when it came to making money.
            "Sounds Chinese," said the artist.
            "I've heard of 'pom-pom,' remarked BiUy.
            "That's a sort of big gun which makes a funny
            noise." Billy had ence had the idea of beeoininj
            a military man. "But ping-pon^r— that's a new
            one on me."
            "Some new style of bridge. I suppose." mut
            tered the artist. "It's not for me. I've sacri
            ficed enough on that altar."
            "Well. I'm going up to play ping-pong," an
            nounced the youth. "I don't care what it is, tit
            name's new. Better come along. Jack. You
            were growling a minute ago about there being
            nothing new, and here you are."
            Dilly went to Harriet's and played ping-pong,
            and when he had not retumeO by midnight th«
            other fellows knew that he was enjoying it. H«
            would not tell them what the new game was
            when he finally put in an appearance, but ad
            vised them to find out for themselves.
            An indoor edition of tennis is ping-pong, til*
            name coming from the curious sound which tie
            parchment rackets give forth when they striis
            the little balls. It is played on the dining room
            taMe, across the centre of which a low net is
            stretched. Th> rules are almost the same as
            in tennis, and the points are counted tennis
            fashion. There is even mure chance for skilful
            handling of the ball than In outduor game*
            and there are tricks innumerable which add
            interest and variety. Skilful players can ii??
            up the volleying process until interest reaches
            fever pitch. It is almost as exciting for tie
            spectators as for the players, which U core
            than can be said of tennis.
            It is an absorbing game, as the EngHsh S«l
            tell you. It his been played i:i London ilisisj
            romis for the last two or three years; but ha
            never been strictly in vogue until this winter
            The ollieers of the British army carried pir.g
            peng sets to South Africa with t'.u-m. and have
            set up their tab) on tho wldt when the Ecea
            let them remain Ln camp long enough.
            Why the game has not taken hold in tiia
            country is something which Americans who live
            In London cannot understand. They have writ
            ten home about the beauties and delisht3 o! v
            ping-pong. They laud it to the skies for tie
            exercise it affords to busy c.tn who have o
            work in offices all day. and to women who
            occupied with a round of teas a^d recepucsi
            PING-PONG.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86071197/1902-03-02/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=fad+table+tennis&amp;r=-1.114,-0.075,3.228,1.464,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90059523/1902-04-06/ed-1/?sp=23&amp;q=ping-pong+table+tennis&amp;r=-0.326,0.178,1.969,0.893,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016357/1902-05-03/ed-1/?sp=7&amp;q=PING-PONG+ping+pong+craze&amp;r=-1.345,-0.063,3.69,1.674,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Our greatest demand for complete completesets completesets completesets
              sets including the regulation tables tableshas tableshas tableshas
              has of course come from the clubs clubssaid clubssnld clubssaid
              said a dealer yesterday But the thewomen thcwomcn thewomen
              women women and children hare got the thefever thetever thefever
              fever as bad ba as their brothers and andfathers andtathers andfathers
              fathers If youre writing about the thepingpong theplngl1011g theping
              pingpong ping pong craze you cant make it t too toostrong oo oostrong oostrong
              strong So far as I know we havent haventsold haventsold haventsold
              sold a set to any old ladles la les home yet yetbut yetbut yetbut
              but I dare are say the game will reach reachthem reachthem reachthem
              them in time This craze beats any anything anything anything
              thing I ever heard of Our belief is isthat Isthat Isthat
              that its only beginning Hot weather weathermay weathermay weathermay
              may affect our sales somewhat but butwo butwe
              wo look for an increased demand next nextfall nextfall nextfall
              fall fallOur
              Our indoor putting green In the theback theback theback
              back of the th store has been occupied by bya bya
              a pingpong ping poug table for several weeks weeksLfits weeksL weeksLets
              Lets L ts of people who never saw the thegame thegame thegame
              game come In here and watch a few fewsets fewsets fewsets
              sets get fascinated by the play and nndcud riudend andend
              end by buying racquets and balls anda and anda anda
              a net to take home and set up on their theirdiningroom theIrdlnlngroom theirdining
              diningroom dining room or billiard table Theres Theresa
              a game going on here almost every everyhour ceryhOUl everyhour
              hour of the day People cant seem to toget toget toget
              get enough of IL ILThe It ItTho ItTho
              Tho clubs have been and are still stilltlys stillt10 stilltl
              tlys t10 tl o stronghold of the craze although althoughthe nlthouhtho althoughthe
              the newspapers have had more to say sayabout sayabout sayabout
              about the play In brokers ofllces of lces and andon andon andon
              on ocean steamers So sudden has been beenthe beenthe beenthe
              the passion for the sport and so much muchroom muchroom muchrOonl
              room does a regulation table take up upthat upthat upthat
              that most of the clubs have had to togive togive togive
              give up some other sport in whole or orIn 01In orin
              In part for a time or else sacrifice sacrificepart sacrltleepart sacrificepart
              part of their diningroom space No Nobody Nobody Nobody
              body seems to object however Even Eventho Erentho Eventhe
              tho most sedate of club loungers al although nltbough although
              though he may begin by scoffing at atthe atthe atthe
              the childs play ends in becoming becomingcither becomIngeither becomingeither
              either an enthusiast entllUslastor or a disappointed disappointedbut lsappolnledbut
              but persistent duffer dufferCollege dufferCollega dufferCollege
              College clubs or other clubs fre frequented tree treequented frequented
              quented by younger men are the worst worstsufferers worstsufferers worstsufferers
              sufferers from the pingpong ping pong malady maladyTho maladylo maladyI1he
              I1he Tho lo Harvard 1 alvald Club early In Inthcwlutol Inthcwlutolput the winter winterput winterput
              put up the little nets on its billiard billiardtables bllliardtables billiardtables
              tables and billiards have scarcely
              been played there since Members Memberspay Memberspay Iemberlpay
              pay the same amount per hour for forplaying forplayIng forplaying
              playing pingpong ping pong that they formerly formerlywere 1ormerl 1ormerlwero formerlywere
              were cbnrgdtl for fortbe the use of the bit billiard bllliard bitHard
              liard tables The club has since set up upIn upIn upin
              In addition a veal ping pingpong pong board boardThe boardThe boardThe
              The Yale Club has four tables in one oneof oneot oneof
              of the class diningrooms on the ninth ninthfloor ninthfioor ninthfloor
              floor The Cornell University Club Clubgives Clubgives Clubgives
              gives up half Its diningroom to the thopastime thepastime thepastime
              pastime and the House UouseOommlttee UouseOommltteenow Committee Committeenow Committeenow
              now talks of letting the whole apart apartment apattment apartment
              ment bo used for It so many of the themembers themembers themembers
              members want to play and pingpong pingpongtables plngpongtables ping pong pongtables
              tables can be used ns dining lnlnl tables if ifit ItIt ifit
              it takes too long to make the change changeIn changeIn changeIn
              In n Brooklyn Droold n athletic club the ping plugpongcrs pingpongers pingpongers
              pongers have Invaded the the handball handballcourt handballcourt handballcourt
              court Most of these resorts Ies rts have had hador hador hador
              or are having pingpong ping pong tdurnamentsand tdurnaments tournamentsnnd
              nnd clever players bare Jave been dowel developed deeloped doweloped
              oped in the course of a few weeks weeksBoardinghouses weeksBoardinghouses weeksBoardinghouses
              Boardinghouses In all parts of town townhave townhave townhave
              have been hard hit by the craze The Thelong ihelong Thelong
              long table ta ble in the back parlor l llor makes a agood agood agood
              good pingpong pl ping gllong pong board and a till the young youngman youngman youngman
              man In the hall bedroom two flights flightsup filghtsup flightsup
              up takes delight In making the star starboarder starboatder starboarder
              boarder look like thirty cents The Thelandladies Thelandladies rholandladIes
              landladies are arc rc not enthusiastic overthe over overthe 001the
              the game because when played In the theevening theevening theevening
              evening it has a n tendency to develop developa developrobust
              a robust appetite for late suppersThe suppers suppersThe suppersThe
              The vernacular of tbo sport has not notyet notyet notyet
              yet reached a l high degree of development develop development oelop11ent
              ment For the present as Is the case casewith casewltbany casewith
              wltbany with any new game players make free freewith treewltb freewith
              with words nnd phrases plll ses proper to toother toother toother
              other branches of sport Expressions Expressionslike Expressionslike
              like You dealt cm the last time timeThis timeThis timeThis
              This cue Is rotten Off side are areheard areIleard areheard
              heard around the board Picturesque Picturesquelanguage Plctulesquelanguage Picturesquelanguage
              language of n different character is isalso Isnlso isalso
              also common The elusive celluloid celluloidsphere celluloidsphere celluloidsphere
              sphere is as conducive to profanity as nsthe asthe asthe
              the guttn guttnpercha percha A well known lawn lawntennis lawntennis lawntennis
              tennis player has n novelty in the way wayof wayof wayof
              of pingpong ping pong profanity When he hemakes hemakes hemakes
              makes a fault he shouts Fudge I or orGoodness 01Goollness oreGoodness
              Goodness gracious
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016353/1902-05-11/ed-1/?sp=2&amp;q=table+tennis&amp;st=text&amp;r=-0.266,-0.027,1.533,1.533,0</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84020274/1902-05-18/ed-1/?sp=46&amp;q=PING+PONG+ping+pong+ping-pong&amp;r=-1.155,-0.002,3.31,1.501,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Wher
              ever there is room for a dining table therfj
              is room for ping-pong, and tho fascination
              that the gamo nor. holds, especially amon
              tho smart set. cannot bo downed by warn;
              m cather.
              Among tho particularly pood plng-ponr;
              rooms in bt, Louis, asldo from tho clubs,
              are those at tho Drummond's. Mis Wtck
              him's and at tho McKittrick's. Cvery evo
              ning ping-pong holda sway. It is proper
              nowadays for young ladies to take soma
              form of physical exercise, and ping-ponB
              combines all the pleasure that they- may
              find in any exercise and affords all tha
              sport of play. j
              Ralph and Walter McKittrlck, Arthua
              Shepley and Dan KIrby- are among the best
              and most enthusiastic players In the city.
              The Country Club and tho Florissant Club
              are utterly crazed over tho game. At pres
              ent It holds the trumps over all other
              games, and from Indications it will be tha
              popular game of the summer at both clubs.
              Of course, this does not mean that tenn!
              and golf and polo will not havo their de
              votees, but ping-pong will bo tho most frequently-
              played gamo of tho season.
              The women of the city are us enthusias
              tic .as the men-possibly more so. and they
              havo their claims upon the attention of tho
              men and their sports. Ping-pong looks and
              sounds llko a game that does not requira
              as much cndtiranco and strength as other11
              spons anu tint is sid to bo tho reuson
              that the women have taken It up. As t,
              matter ot fact. It is as violent as nlmnst
              any gamo th it Is popular with many peo
              ple, but It seems so playful that tho weaker
              be. have seized upon It.
              It is a fact that one business man of this
              c ty a man or more than usual corpulence-
              has reduced his weight by forty pounds
              playing ping-pong. And If the truth mi.ro
              known, it is probably true tint several
              women have been enabled to become mora
              sylph-like through the medium of the game.
              But that Is .v matter concerning which
              women will not talk.
              Women who are onenlv .anient nl.-ners
              of
              ny
              ping-pong are rot the ones of whom any
              one can say they play to reduce thel
              weight. They- are modern women In every
              may, and have taken up tho game not only
              because it Is tho fad, but also because it
              Is a g ime that enables them to keep In
              good physical condition It is proper no
              longer for momtn to be weak and requiring
              the attention of maids and menr but they
              mut be able to cope with the strongest.
              Accordingly, they tako as much exercise,
              comparatively, as men And ping-pong of
              fers them something in the way of a gam
              that has not been offered by any thins
              else.
              Among the more prominent women play
              ers of ping-pong are Mrs. James Drurr
              mond, Mrs. William' Gregg, Mri. Laurence
              J. Mornn MIs ickham. Mis Mitchell.
              Mrs. E O. Stanard, Mrs. W. II. Walker
              and Mrs. Goodman King. Each of theso
              has an elaborate ping-pong room fitted up
              nt her house, and parties are frequent. It
              is not at nit unusual for them to meet in
              the morning and play arduously befora
              luncheon. It serves as an excellent appe
              tizer. The game was hroiight 'to St. Louis by
              two people at about the same time. Mrs.
              E. H. Semple ot Westminster place be
              came enamored of the game while abroad
              last summer, and when she returned she
              set up a table at once. Sirs. Sidney Walker
              appeared on the scene at about the sama
              time, an enthusiastic player of the game.
              That mas its start In thi3 city. It did not
              take long to bring the sport to its present
              position, but these two St. Louisans havo
              been instrumental In making it a fad.
              One of the best players among the women
              is Mrs. Lewis Haywood She has for sev
              eral months been a devotee, and lias ac
              quired remarkable 'kill in handling tho
              racquet. Mrs. John Fowler Is another ex
              cellent player, and Mrc Dan Taylor, Mrs,
              Campbell Smith and Mrs. Frank HammeS
              are also in the first class.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90059523/1902-05-25/ed-1/?sp=21&amp;q=daft+ping-pong</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              DAFT ON PING-PONG
              Washington Entranced With
              Game, Which Is Played
              in Many Homes
              'fcOOM OF TIGHT CORSET
              f(Xew Diversion Has Phenotncnal
              Hold on All Sort* and Condi-
              tion*. From 9teM Senators
              tv DudtliiiK Debutantes.
              Special to The Globe.
              WASHINGTON, D. C. May 21.—Mover
              j lias the national capital been so com-
              T-letely enslaved by the fascinations of a
              game, indoor or outdoor, as it has fallen
              (under the seductive influence of the won
              jdc-rful new game, which, having set all
              J l^ngland crazy, has come with- a power
              to] stride across the Atlantic to exercise
              its potent influence upon our social life.
              i As a prominent leader of Washington
              I society remarked the other day, "Wash
              ington has fairly gone ping-pong mad."
              Conversation in capital society has now
              i foe-come impregnated with the peculiar
              I terms of the new pastime. Where for
              merly one would hear "social precedence"
              and "rising man," one now hears "clever
              i (half volleyer" and "invincible striker
              I out."
              "Love" and "advantage" as topics of
              social conversation have now a ping-pong
              significance entirely foreign to their for
              xtx-r meaning among the capital gossips.
              The ping-pong party has entirely sup
              planted the whist party arid the bridge
              circle.
              The peculiar ping-pong of the celluloid
              balls as they are beaten to and fro (from
              ■which the game derives its name) is now
              to be heard j in every Washington home
              from the palatial mansion of the fam
              -1 ily of the men who shape the nation's.
              I destiny on Pennsylvania avenue to the
              humble residence of the congressional
              I bootblack in the eastern section of the
              i city. Years are a matter of no consid
              ©ration among the devotees of the sport.
              The mature matron whose nod or frown
              I Oias settled one way or the other the so
              cial aspirations of mar.v- a newcomer
              .at the capital is as frequently to be seen
              i exerting herself in a manner wonderful
              to behold, to keep the little swiftly pass- j
              ing celluloid ball from dropping on her
              I side of the net, as is the beautiful bud
              ding debutante who, with flushed face,
              eyes sparkling with enthusiasm- and ex
              citement. and bared arms wildly but
              Withal skillfully circling the air, is a
              cSaily testimonial to the aethestic features
              of the game.
              Strike* nil Classes.
              Nor are the enthusiasts of the new
              gam" to be found only among the fairer
              sex, Washington masculinity has given
              itself to ping-pong with an abandon
              ,Nor ar^ the enthusiasts .of the now
              which would furnish a profitable study to
              the seeker- of pysehologieal phenomena.
              Staid congressmen, dignified senators.
              Learned members of the bench and bar
              When they meet together nowadays dis
              cuss not, the political significance of the
              lim.s. but the latest-make of ping-pong
              racquet.
              This -may be regarded as gross exagger
              ation. It is a potent fact, however, that
              ping p has attained a surprising vogue
              ■among Washington's public men.
              All the leading hotels and cafes are
              hastening to open up ping-pong parlors
              on their premises, so that their distin
              guished patrons may indulge .to their
              heart's content in the game.
              Senator Maur.a. when asked the other'
              ■day whether he favored the. erection of aj
              ping-pong parlor in the national capital,
              l>uckercd up.his brow* and gave the mat
              tor a few minutes' serious consideration
              before discussing the idea with a smile.
              Congressman Sulzer, when asked to ex
              plain the tremendous hold that ping-pong
              has taken upon members of the-house,
              said that it is a wonderful game for~ex
              erclse. and gives one a good hand to
              sustain the handshaking proclivities of
              the vast army of well meaning citizens
              who swoop down upon unwilling repre
              sentatives of the people with all the re
              lentless energy of the notorious New
              Jersey musquito upon its helpless victim.
              As may be supposed, the stores have
              not been slow to take advantage of the
              commercial possibilities of the craze. In
              -addition to the fact that some of the
              larger dry goods emporiums are opening
              up ping-pong saloons for the accommo
              dation of their patrons, the new game
              has an important bearing upon the latest
              styles. The ping-pong waist is prom
              inently- displayed in the shop windows,
              find is a phenomenal seller; while the
              new forms of neckwear for women and
              men bear handsomely embroidered figure.*
              ■of ping-pong racquets and balls upon
              their silken folds.
              Doom of the Tight Corset.
              One important reform the game prom,
              ises to effect, which may render rational,
              the development which has been lavished'
              upon it by England and America and im
              mortalize the new game as one of the
              most valuable and beneficent reform fac
              tors of the century.
              Ping-pong may abolish the tight laced
              ■corset.
              Ping-pong is essentially an informal
              game to be played at the spur of the
              moment, as the whim seizes. It is a
              game to be introduced by the smiling
              hostess after the last vestige of the din
              "■ner has been cleared away and ti;o
              white table cloth is removed to make
              way for the ping-pong net. Consequently
              as the rapid movement and freedom of
              body S necessary to me ping-pong player
              renders the corset impossible, the charm
              ing diner out has either to leave off her
              corsets when she dresses to attend a
              modern dim party or run the risk of
              having to stand against the wall in ail
              the-prim symmetry of a corseted waist
              and, watch the merry movements of her
              more fortunate sisters who, with grace
              fully swing forms, keep the merry cellu
              loid ball ping-ponging across the table
              at a lively pace to the intense admira
              tion of the man with the racquet on th^
              other side of the table and .every other
              man In the room. v
              This good may ping-pong do; bu other
              wise what peculiar qualities has the same
              to '-rive it phenomenal popularity? Strict
              ly speaking it is nothing more or less
              then a table adaptation of lawn tennis
              and tennis, while possessing to an equal
              and even greater degree the same physi
              cal benefits and sporting fascinations of
              its replica has never attained the vogue
              which has been vouchsafed to ping-pong.
              Played on Dining Table.
              Ping-pong is played on an ordinary din-
              Ing table and its only accessories are
              posts tp hold the net, the net itself
              vellum string or wood-racquets and cellu-
              loid balls: The game is for two people
              one standing on one end of the table,
              the other opposite. The player who first
              delivers the ball is called the server The
              Other the striker out. i The service is
              strictly underhand and is delivered from
              beyond the end of the table.
              The: ball served must drop on the table
              beyond the net and is then in piav. if
              it dops into the net or off the table it
              counts to the striker out
              The server wins a stroke if the striker
              out fails to return the service or ball in
              play of the table.
              The striker out wins a stroke If the
              server fails to return the ball in play or
              makes a foul in service.
              On either player winning his first stroke
              the score la 15. The second stroke brings
              the score to 30; the third stroke is called
              •40 and the fourth stroke wins a game
              The player who wins the first six games
              -wins a set.-
              This is all there really is to the game
              of ping-pong. Certainly it Is a skill de
              manding and skill acquiring game. It
              lias simplicity and cheapness to recom
              mend it. It is far better from a hygenie
              standpoint than a majority of parlor
              prames and is an extremely socialble and
              interesting pastime. It is. for these rea
              sons and its similarity to tennis, a game
              calculated to prove attractive to the"
              younger members of both sexes.
              But why It has set the people of two
              countries almost crazy: why old as well
              as young-have taken up ping-pong when
              they would not as much as look at an-
              Our Opening of Summer fliilinery.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1902-06-01/ed-1/?sp=13&amp;q=PING-PONG&amp;r=-0.252,0.339,1.717,0.779,0</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              "It has been said that the muscles of
              the legs and arms are often wearied By
              the game. This .is true in a. sense, but I
              think that the eye and the brain -will be
              exhausted :n ping-pong long before the
              muscles used in sending and returning
              balls can be affected to any appreciable
              extent."
              ISEASES with strange names have
              Dloliowtd in the wake of ping-pong,
              J.ut the real pang is not a fanciful
              une. for the watching of the cellu
              loid* sphere really strains the eyes.
              Let London surgeons talk as they will
              about tei.dosyr.ovitis "and p^ig-ponS an
              kles: all these are as nothing compared
              to tho'strair.ed muscles of the eye of the
              Ail ping-pong devotees, even experts,
              suffer from the ping-pong eye more or
              Jess. Other muscles employed to playing
              th* game are ""speedily co-ordinated. To
              develop a proper technique is^ing-pong
              is no easy matter, and in the endeavor
              the eye suffers the most.
              There is a ping-pong wrist, of course,
              and a ping-pong back, but the player who
              can return a ball a hundred times or so
              suffers comparatively little from these.
              The tyro who bends often to pick up the
              balls -which bound upon the carpet is the
              one who is most likely to complain of
              In time he learns, however, to make the
              optical nerves save the exertions of the
              muscles. Then he requires a ping-pony
              i ji^jlimii
              Not much strength is required in tho
              game. A little more vigorous than bil
              liards and not quite bo arduous as tennis.
              of which it is a cousin german, pins-
              THE S U^J)AY CALL.
              pcng appeals to those who have the quick
              eye.
              The skillful player can keep his body
              almost rigid, and standing In front of the
              table send the ball backward and forward
              with scarcely a movement of a muscle
              except those of the wrists. Many or the
              players are able- to sit In one of the
              chairs such as are used by spectators in
              billiard games, and still keep the ball go
              ing rapidly.
              Physicians say that many ping-pong
              players suffer from an inflammation of
              the eye. and champion players add their
              Testimony. The constant watching of the
              ball is liable to cause heaoaclies, or, 'in
              other words, to cause irritation to spread
              from the overworked optical mu.-des.
              The pir.g-ro"g eye is often bloodshot.
              The only way to cure it is to stop play
              ing and to give the overworked eye a
              chance to rest. Th!s the ping-pong devo
              te*- objects to doing. When ho becomes
              absorbed in the game he persists in play
              ing it in season and out of season.
              There are many ping-pong table's which
              served originally in dining-rooms. The
              man who plays upon them is prone fo
              contract the ping-pong eye. The ideal
              table should be dark green^This color is
              easy on the eye. A retired billiard or
              poo! table is well adapted to the game,
              as far*"as the effect upon the eye is con
              cerned. The ball is dazzling white.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84020274/1902-07-13/ed-1/?sp=39&amp;q=ping-pong</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1902-09-21/ed-1/?sp=11&amp;q=ping-pong</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              It Is the reactionary influence of ping
              pong on tennis Itself that Is «o surpris
              ing, for In a greater degree a far greater
              degree— than Is generally supposed ping
              pong is responsible for the sudden and
              growing popularity of tennis In the courts
              at Golden Gate Park.
              solely of the possibilities for dainty
              rowEic* which it afforded, nor of the
              .hitherto unsuspected opportunities for
              'flirtations that resulted seriously. There
              would be no need to epeak of those things
              here. Every girl learned them for herself
              very early in the ping-pong craze, and
              made the most of the game.
              PING-PONG, childish Imitation of
              tennis though It is. has done won
              ders for our sex. Every girl ought
              to be'* very clad that she learned
              It, though I'm not thinking now
              Then there is the underhand drive,
              wherein you bring the racquet round and
              up, knocking the ball high above the net
              for a volley serve. In executing the
              underhand drive, take lots of time and
              don't strike the ball until It Is falling close
              to the ground.
          </text>
      </result>
      <!-- 5 additinal -->
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88064676/1902-05-22/ed-1/?sp=6&amp;q=ping+pong+craze</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              The Craze for Ping-Pong.
              Ping pong continues the craze in
              England. Recently a big tournament
              was held in the town hall at Leeds
              for the benefit of the local war relief
              fund. Twelve tables for the game were
              gathered in the large room, which
              was densely packed with spectators.
              The fever, too, rages among the offi
              cers of the navy and the game is
              played regularly in the evenings after
              dinner. The junior midshipmen act
              as caddies, and with the pitching of
              the ships the young men have lots of
              fun retrieving balls that bound from
              the tables.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84022060/1902-05-22/ed-1/?sp=3&amp;q=ping+pong+craze</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              The ping pong craze has reached Carson
              and Reno.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83016025/1902-08-13/ed-1/?sp=1&amp;q=ping+pong+craze</id>
          <rel>1</rel>
          <text>
              Ping Pong
              are certainly the two most popu
              lar games just at present. And
              everything points to a lasting pop
              ularity for both. It:s a fact that
              the Ping Pong craze has given
              Tennis a boom unsurpassed in
              the history of the game. Wo
              carry All of the Better Grades of
              Tennis and Ping Pong Goods.
          </text>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/ca05000846/1903-07-16/ed-1/?sp=4&amp;q=ping+pong+craze</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
      <result>
          <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016014/1902-06-28/ed-1/?sp=8&amp;q=ping+pong+craze</id>
          <rel>0</rel>
      </result>
    </results>
  </topic>
</topics>
